export const alcatrazDayTourAccordianData = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "Do I need to book the Alcatraz Day Tour in advance?",
    answer:
      "Yeah, mostly. Tours often sell out days or even weeks ahead, especially during summer and holiday periods. We suggest you reserve tickets in advance so you don't miss this amazing day tour of Alcatraz.",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "How long is the Alcatraz Day Tour?",
    answer:
      "The Alcatraz Island tour routinely lasts around 2.5 to 3 hours. This includes ferry travel and the island's full tour. As per customer reviews, it's enough time to explore and enjoy the island's beauty.",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: "What is included in the Day Tour of Alcartraz Island ticket?",
    answer:
      "The ticket includes a fully guided ferry service, entry to the island, and the superior audio tour of the cellhouse. This also includes access to all indoor and outdoor places to explore.",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "How long should I plan for the full visit?",
    answer:
      "To fully benefit from the Alcartraz Island day tour, you should plan your day on site for approximately 4 hours. This will give you time to explore indoor and outdoor spaces like Eagle Plaza, the Recreation Yard, the Sallyport, and the Rose Garden, etc.",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "How often do ferries run and what are the departure times?",
    answer:
      "Ferries run every 30 to 40 minutes from morning to early evening. Schedules may vary slightly by season. The time duration for a day tour is, like, from 8:40 AM to 3:50 PM, and for Alcatraz night tour, time is Tuesdays-Saturdays (5:55pm, 6:30pm, and 7:05pm).",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "Can I stay on the island as long as I like?",
    answer:
      "You can remain on the island as long as you like until the last scheduled return ferry. But yeah, overnight stays are not allowed.",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "Is food available on the island?",
    answer:
      "There is no food service on Alcatraz itself. However, you can carry your snacks with you in designated areas. Food is available at Pier 33 before departure.",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "Is the audio tour included, and in what languages?",
    answer:
      "Yeah! The audio tour is included in the ticket and is available in English, Spanish, French, German, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Mandarin, Dutch, and Portuguese.",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question: "How many tickets can one person purchase at once?",
    answer:
      "A person can buy up to 8 tickets. Tickets for Alcartaz day tour can be purchased per person. Group reservations for Alcartaz tour for more than 8 require special arrangements. You can contact us for this. ",
  },
];

export const alcatrazNightTourAccordianData = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "What time does the Alcatraz Night Tour depart?",
    answer:
      "The Alcatraz night tour leaves around 5:55 PM to 6:30 PM. Exact timing basically depends on the season. But yeah, do check your Alcatraz night tour tickets and try to arrive even before the time.",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "On which days is the Night Tour available?",
    answer:
      "Night time tour of Alcatraz runs Tuesday to Saturday. There are no Alcatraz night tours on Sundays and Mondays.",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: "How long is the Alcatraz Night Tour?",
    answer:
      "The Alcatraz Island night tour takes 2-3 hours. Ferries return by 9:30 PM or 10:00 PM. It depends on the schedule. Although the tour normally lasts for 2-3 hours, but you can enjoy it there till the last ferry departure time (normally 9:30 PM). Do keep in mind, no overnight stays are allowed.",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "How many people are on the Night Tour?",
    answer:
      "Night tour of Alcatraz has limited tickets, about 700 people per night, which is far fewer than daytime tours.",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "What is included in the Alcatraz Night Tour?",
    answer:
      "Alcatraz night tour includes ferry trip (complete, to and from), cellhouse audio tour, special programs, guided talks, and evening access to special places like the hospital wing, secret cell blocks, Civil War buildings, gardens (which are not included in the day tour).",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "Do I need to book the Alcatraz Night Tour in advance?",
    answer:
      "Yeah, mostly. Tours often sell out days or even weeks ahead, especially during summer and holiday periods. We suggest you reserve tickets in advance so you don't miss this amazing tour of Alcatraz.",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "How long should I plan for the full visit?",
    answer:
      "To fully benefit from the Alcartraz Island night tour, you should plan for approximately 4 hours. This will give you time to explore indoor and outdoor spaces like Eagle Plaza, the Recreation Yard, the Sallyport, and the Rose Garden etc.",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "How often do ferries run and what are the departure times?",
    answer:
      "Ferries run every 30 to 40 minutes. Schedules may vary slightly by season. The time duration for a night tour is, like, from 5:55pm, 6:30pm, and 7:05pm on Tuesdays - Saturdays, and for the Alcatraz day tour, the time is about 8:40 AM to 3:50 PM.",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question: "Can I stay on the island as long as I like?",
    answer:
      "You can remain on the island as long as you like until the last scheduled return ferry. But yeah, overnight stays are not allowed.",
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: "Is food available on the island?",
    answer:
      "There is no food service on Alcatraz itself. However, you can carry your snacks with you in designated areas. Food is available at Pier 33 before departure. Alcohols are not allowed, as they sell on the ferry return.",
  },
  {
    id: "11",
    question: "Is the audio tour included, and in what languages?",
    answer:
      "Yeah! The audio tour is included in the ticket and is available in English, Spanish, French, German, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Mandarin, Dutch, and Portuguese.",
  },
  {
    id: "12",
    question: "How many tickets can one person purchase at once?",
    answer:
      "A person can buy up to 8 tickets. Tickets for the Alcatraz night tour can be purchased per person. Group reservations for the Alcatraz tour for more than 8 require special arrangements. You can contact us for this.",
  },
];

export const landingPageAccordianData = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "Do I need to book the Alcatraz Tour in advance?",
    answer:
      "Yeah, mostly. Tours often sell out days or even weeks ahead, especially during summer and holiday periods. We suggest you reserve tickets in advance so you don't miss this amazing tour of Alcatraz.",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "How do I purchase a Ticket?",
    answer:
      "Simply choose your date & time and book directly from our website. Only card payments are allowed; no cash. And yes, the tickets should be in the name of the attendee. During the tour, the person whose name is present on the ticket should be there with a valid ID.",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question:
      "How do I book Alcatraz tickets as a tour operator or travel agent?",
    answer:
      "Even if you are a travel agent or operator, you still need to book the ticket in the client's name and credit card.",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "How often do ferries run and what are the departure times?",
    answer:
      "Ferries run every 30 to 40 minutes from morning to early evening. Schedules may vary slightly by season. The time duration for a day tour is, like, from 8:40 AM to 3:50 PM, and for Alcatraz night tour, time is Tuesdays-Saturdays (5:55pm, 6:30pm, and 7:05pm).",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "What if I miss my ferry?",
    answer:
      "If you miss your ferry to Alcatraz, you cannot have another one. Tickets are for a specific period of time. In case you miss it, you lose your tour to Alcatraz Island. Then you need to book a new ticket.",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "Can I reschedule or get a refund?",
    answer:
      "Reschedule and refund options are only available if you inform us minimum 72 hours before your departure time. Then you can have your refund. In any other case, a refund is not possible or allowed.",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "Are National Park Passes accepted?",
    answer: "No, National Park Passes are not acceptable.",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "Is food available on the island?",
    answer:
      "No, food is not available on the Island. You can buy food and drinks before arriving at the ferry. Eating on the Island is not permitted in some areas, but you can have a water bottle or snacks with you.",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question: "Which languages are supported for the audio tour?",
    answer:
      "An audio tour is available in 10 languages. These include English, Spanish, French, German, Italian, Japanese, Dutch, Mandarin, Portuguese, and Korean.",
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: "When does Alcatraz open and close during the year?",
    answer:
      "Alcatraz is open 12 months a year except for holidays (Thanksgiving, Christmas, and New Year's Day). But opening hours may change as per the season.",
  },
  {
    id: "11",
    question: "Is Alcatraz accessible for people with mobility needs?",
    answer:
      "Yes, Alcatraz offers a tram service called SEAT for visitors with limited mobility. Paths and facilities are mostly wheelchair-friendly. We try all our best to open our gates to everyone.",
  },
  {
    id: "12",
    question: "Do I need an ID or the credit card used to book?",
    answer:
      "Yes. The primary ticket holder must bring a photo ID and the card used for purchase, especially when collecting tickets on-site.",
  },
  {
    id: "13",
    question: "Can tickets be cancelled or rescheduled?",
    answer:
      "Tickets are non-refundable, but some rescheduling options may be available depending on availability and how far in advance the request is made. May discuss with the customer service team.",
  },
  {
    id: "14",
    question: "Are toddlers free?",
    answer:
      "Kids under age 5 get in free of charge, but they still need a valid entry ticket.",
  },
  {
    id: "15",
    question: "Are minors allowed without an adult?",
    answer:
      "No, children under 18 must be accompanied by an adult guardian at all times during the Alcatraz Day trip.",
  },
];
